https://www.icisa.org/cookie-policy-eu/

This Cookie Policy was last updated on 6 March 2020 and applies to citizens of the European Economic Area.1. IntroductionOur website, https://www.icisa.org (hereinafter: "the website") uses cookies and other related technologies (for convenience all technologies are referred to as "cookies"). Cookies are also placed by third parties we have engaged. In the document below we inform you about the use of cookies on our website.2. What are cookies?A cookie is a small simple file that is sent along with pages of this website and stored by your browser on the hard drive of your computer or another device. The information stored therein may be returned to our servers or to the servers of the relevant third parties during a subsequent visit.3. What are scripts?A script is a piece of program code that is used to make our website function properly and interactively. This code is executed on our server or on your device.4. What is a web beacon?A web beacon (or a pixel tag) is a small, invisible piece of text or image on a website that is used to monitor traffic on a website. In order to do this, various data about you is stored using web beacons.5. Cookies5.1 Technical or functional cookiesSome cookies ensure that certain parts of the website work properly and that your user preferences remain known. By placing functional cookies, we make it easier for you to visit our website. This way, you do not need to repeatedly enter the same information when visiting our website and, for example, the items remain in your shopping cart until you have paid. We may place these cookies without your consent.5.2 Analytical cookiesWe use analytical cookies to optimize the website experience for our users. With these analytical cookies we get insights in the usage of our website. We ask your permission to place analytical cookies.5.3 Marketing/Tracking cookiesMarketing/Tracking cookies are cookies or any other form of local storage, used to create user profiles to display advertising or to track the user on this website or across several websites for similar marketing purposes.6. Placed cookiesGoogle Analytics
Usage
We use Google Analytics for website statistics.
Sharing data
For more information, please read the Google Analytics Privacy Statement.
Statistics (anonymous)
Name
_ga
Retention
2 years
Function
Store a unique user ID
Name
_gid
Usage
We use Cookie Notice for GDPR for cookie consent management.
Sharing data
This data is not shared with third parties.
Functional
Name
cookie_notice_accepted
Retention
persistent
Function
Checks if cookies can be placed
SiteGround
Usage
We use SiteGround for website hosting.
Sharing data
For more information, please read the SiteGround Privacy Statement.
Functional
Name
wpSGCacheBypass
Retention
persistent
Function
WordFence
Usage
We use WordFence for website security.
Sharing data
For more information, please read the WordFence Privacy Statement.
Purpose pending investigation
Name
wfwaf-authcookie-*
Retention
Function
Google Fonts
Usage
We use Google Fonts for display of webfonts.
Sharing data
For more information, please read the Google Fonts Privacy Statement.
Marketing/Tracking
Name
Google Fonts API
Retention
none
Function
Request user IP address
Miscellaneous
Name
persist:hs-beacon-message-44cc73fb-7636-4206-b115-c7b33823551b
Retention
Function
Name
persist:hs-beacon-44cc73fb-7636-4206-b115-c7b33823551b
Retention
Function
Name
wistia
Function
7. ConsentWhen you visit our website for the first time, we will show you a pop-up with an explanation about cookies. As soon as you click on "Accept all cookies", you consent to us using all cookies and plug-ins as described in the pop-up and this Cookie Policy. You can disable the use of cookies via your browser, but please note that our website may no longer work properly.7.1 Manage your consent settings8. Your rights with respect to personal dataYou have the following rights with respect to your personal data:
You have the right to know why your personal data is needed, what will happen to it, and how long it will be retained for.
Right of access: You have the right to access your personal data that is known to us.
Right to rectification: you have the right to supplement, correct, have deleted or blocked your personal data whenever you wish.
If you give us your consent to process your data, you have the right to revoke that consent and to have your personal data deleted.
Right to transfer your data: you have the right to request all your personal data from the controller and transfer it in its entirety to another controller.
Right to object: you may object to the processing of your data. We comply with this, unless there are justified grounds for processing.
To exercise these rights, please contact us. Please refer to the contact details at the bottom of this Cookie Policy. If you have a complaint about how we handle your data, we would like to hear from you, but you also have the right to submit a complaint to the supervisory authority (the Data Protection Authority).9. Enabling/disabling and deleting cookiesYou can use your internet browser to automatically or manually delete cookies. You can also specify that certain cookies may not be placed. Another option is to change the settings of your internet browser so that you receive a message each time a cookie is placed. For more information about these options, please refer to the instructions in the Help section of your browser.Please note that our website may not work properly if all cookies are disabled. If you do delete the cookies in your browser, they will be placed again after your consent when you visit our websites again.10. Contact detailsFor questions and/or comments about our Cookie Policy and this statement, please contact us by using the following contact details:ICISA
Herengracht 473
1017 BS Amsterdam
Netherlands
Netherlands
Website: https://www.icisa.org
Email: secretariat@icisa.org
Phone number: +31 206 254 115This Cookie Policy was synchronized with cookiedatabase.org on 6 March 2020
Cookies on this Website
This site, like many others, uses small files called cookies to help us customize your experience, find out more about cookies and how you can control them.
This page contains information on what ‘cookies’ are, the cookies used by the ICISA, how to switch cookies off in your browser and some useful links for further reading on the subject. If it does not provide the information you were looking for, or you have any further questions about our use of cookie, please email secretariat@icisa.org.
What are ‘cookies’?
‘Cookies’ are small text files that are stored by the browser (for example, Internet Explorer or Chrome) on your computer or mobile phone. They allow websites to store things like user preferences. You can think of cookies as providing a ‘memory’ for the website, so that it can recognize you when you come back and respond appropriately. How do we use cookies?
A visit to a page on our website may generate the following types of cookie:
Anonymous analytics cookies
Registration cookies
Anonymous analytics cookies:
Every time someone visits our website, software provided by another organization generates an ‘anonymous analytics cookie’. These cookies can tell us whether or not you have visited the site before. Your browser will tell us if you have these cookies and, if you don’t, we generate new ones.
This allows us to track how many individual users we have, and how often they visit the site.
Unless you are signed in we cannot use these cookies to identify individuals. We use them to gather statistics, for example, the number of visits to a page. If you are logged in, we will also know the details you gave to us for this, such as your username and email address.
Registration cookies:
When you register with the Website we generate cookies that let us know whether you are signed in or not.
Our servers use these cookies to work out which account you are signed in with, and if you are allowed access to a particular service. It also allows us to associate any comments you post with your username. If you have not selected ‘keep me signed in’, your cookies get deleted when you either close your browser or shut down your computer.
While you are signed into either of the sites, we combine information from your registration cookies with analytics cookies, which we could use to identify which pages you have seen on the BU Website.
How do I turn cookies off?
It is usually possible to stop your browser accepting cookies, or to stop it accepting cookies from a particular website. However, we cannot tell if you are signed in without using cookies, so you would not be able to post comments.
All modern browsers allow you to change your cookie settings. You can usually find these settings in the ‘options’ or ‘preferences’ menu of your browser. To understand these settings, the following links may be helpful, or you can use the ‘Help’ option in your browser for more details.
Cookie settings in Internet ExplorerCookie settings in Firefox
Cookie settings in Chrome Cookie settings in Safari web
Microsoft Cookies guide
All About Cookies
The IAB has provided the following website to give information specifically about privacy issues around Internet advertising:
youronlinechoices.co.uk/uk
For further legal information about privacy issues, you may find these links useful:
Data Protection Act 1998
The Information Commissioner’s Office
If you would like to contact us about cookies please email us at secretariat@icisa.org.
